Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings, 189268
  - Bobkin Lane, circa 1938-1990; 190656 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking North, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5749; 190657; Mandelbaum, Ira; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 1)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking South, circa 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5751; 190658; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Bobkin Lane, Site of Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, Wooster Street and Washington Square South, circa 1938; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5755; 190660; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 6.5 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Varsity Luncheon, Bobkin Lane, Site of Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, West Side of Wooster Street, Looking South from West 4th Street, 1945; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5757; 190661; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 5)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Fair, Bobkin Lane, 1974; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5759; 190662; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Bobkin Lane, Looking South, 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5761; 190663; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Installation, Bobkin Lane, Looking North, circa 1982; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5673; 190664; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Schwartz Plaza, Bobkin Lane, Looking North, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5765; 190665; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Schwartz Plaza, Bobkin Lane, Looking North, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5767; 190666; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Schwartz Plaza, Bobkin Lane, Looking Southwest, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5769; 190667; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Schwartz Plaza, Bobkin Lane, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5771; 190668; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Founders Memorial, Schwartz Plaza, Bobkin Lane, Looking South, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5773; 190669; color print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - West Broadway and West Third, Site of Bobst, Looking Northeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6877; 222417; Sihler, Henry J.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 13a)
    - Bobst Library Site, West Broadway and West Third, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6879; 222418; Sihler, Henry J.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Bobst Library Site, West Fourth and West Broadway, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6881; 222419; Sihler, Henry J.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Bobst Library Site, Wooster Street and Washington Square South, Looking Southwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6883; 222420; Sihler, Henry J.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Site of Bobst Library Prior to Construction, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6885; 222421; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Block Wooster Street and West Broadway, South Side of Washington Square South, Looking East from West Broadway, Site of Bobst Library, April 1945; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6887; 222422; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Block Wooster Street and West Broadway, North side of West Third Street Looking East from West Broadway, Site of Bobst Library, circa 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6889; 222423; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Block Wooster Street and West Broadway, North Side of West Third Street Looking West from Wooster, Site of Bobst Library, April 1945; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6891; 222424; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Bobst Library, Looking Northwest from West Third, April 21, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6893; 222425; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 1, Item 21)
  - Washington Square Book Center (Bookstore), 1938-1984; 200157 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - New York University Bookstore, Washington Place, Looking West, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5779; 200158; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - New York University Book Center, Corner of Washington Place and Greene Street, Looking Southwest, 1969; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5781; 200159; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - New York University Book Center, Corner of Washington Place and Greene Street, Looking South, 1969; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5783; 200160; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Cleaning the Building Facade of the New York University Book Center, Washington Place, 1959; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5785; 200161; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - New York University Book Center, South Side of Washington Place, Looking West from Greene Street, 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5787; 200162; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - New York University Book Center, Southwest Corner of Washington Place and Greene Street, 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5789; 200163; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - New York University Book Center, South Side of Washington Place, Looking West from Greene Street, 1947; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5791; 200164; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - New York University Book Center, Washington Place and Greene Street, circa 1940; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5793; 200165; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - New York University Bookstore, 40-4 WEst 4th Street, 1938; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5795; 200166; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - New York University Book Center, Southwest Corner of Washington Place and Greene Street, 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5797; 200167; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Workman Painting the Facade of the New York University Book Center, 1959; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5799; 200171; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Workmen Cleaning the Facade of the New York University Book Center, 1959; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5801; 200172; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - Abbey Bookshop, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5803; 200173; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - New York University Book Center, Southwest Corner of Washington Place and Greene Street, 1964; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5805; 200174; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Entrance to the New York University Book Store, 1965; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5807; 200175; black-and-white print (photograph), 3.25 x 4.24 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - Student at a Dictionary Display, New York Univeristy Bookstore, 1970; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5809; 200176; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - Students in Line at the New York University Book Center, 1970; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5811; 200220; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - Student Browsing the Book Stacks, Barnes & Noble, 105 5th Avenue at 18th Street, 1971; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5813; 200221; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - Student Browsing the Book Stacks, Barnes & Noble, 105 5th Avenue at 18th Street, 1971; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5815; 200222; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - Students Browsing the Book Stacks, Barnes & Noble,105 5th Avenue at 18th Street, 1971; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5817; 200223; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - Students in Line and Browsing Books, New York University Bookstore, 1972; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5819; 200224; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 21)
    - New York University Book Center Computer, 1979; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5821; 200225; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 6.75 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 22)
    - Exterior of Barnes & Nobles Textbooks, 105 5th Avenue at 18th Street., Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5823; 200226; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 23)
    - Student Reviewing a Textbook, New York Univeristy Bookstore, 1970; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5825; 200227; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 24)
    - Student Checking Out, New York University Book Center, 1970; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5827; 200228; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 25)
    - Entrance, New York University Book Center, 18 Washington Place, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5829; 200229; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 26)
    - John Balagna, Manager of New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5831; 200230; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 27)
    - Student Donating to Oxfam Africa Program, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5833; 200231; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 28)
    - Security Guard at the New York Univeristy Bookstore, circa 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5835; 200258; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 29)
    - Students Browsing Books, New York University Bookstore, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5837; 200259; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 30)
    - Display of George Orwell Books, New York University Book Center, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5839; 200260; black-and-white print (photograph), 3.25 x 4.25 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 31)
    - Student in Line with and Armful of Books, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5841; 200261 (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 32)
      black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches
    - Three Individuals Perusing a Book, Medical School Bookstore, New York University Book Center, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5843; 200262; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 33)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5845; 200263; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 34)
    - Basement Checkout Lines from Security Camera, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5847; 200265; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 35)
    - Students Looking at Books, Aisle 1, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5849; 200266; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 36)
    - Students in Front of the New York University Book Center Entrance, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5851; 200267; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 37)
    - Women Leaving the New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5853; 200268; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 38)
    - Students in an Aisle, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5855; 200269; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 39)
    - Security Guards, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5857; 200270; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 40)
    - Basement Cashier, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5859; 200271; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 41)
    - Book Display, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5861; 200272; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 42)
    - Registers, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5863; 200273; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 43)
    - Two Students in Front of Book Tables, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5865; 200274; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 44)
    - Basement of New York Univeristy Bookstore, Looking Towards Information Desk, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5867; 200275; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 45)
    - Cashier, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5869; 200276; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 46)
    - Basement Aisle, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5871; 200607; Imperatore, India; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 47)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5873; 200608; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 48)
    - Information Desk, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5875; 200609; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 49)
    - Empty Shelves, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5877; 200610; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 50)
    - Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; xNYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5879; 200611; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 51)
    - Basement Security Camera, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5881; 200612; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 52)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5883; 200613; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 53)
    - Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5885; 200614; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 54)
    - Cashier, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5887; 200615; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 55)
    - Barnes and Noble Bookstore, 5th Avenue at 18th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5889; 200616; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 56)
    - Security Camera Monitors, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5891; 200617; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 57)
    - Information Desk, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5892; 200618; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 58)
    - Entrance Turnstiles, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5895; 200619; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 59)
    - Set Your Own Price Book Display, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5897; 200620; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 60)
    - Display of George Orwell Works, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5899; 200621; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 61)
    - Strand Bookstore, 828 Broadway at 12th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5901; 200622; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 62)
    - Entrance, New York University Book Center, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5903; 200623; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 63)
    - All Shoplifters Will Be Prosecuted Sign, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5905; 200624; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 64)
    - Shoplifter Arrested for Stealing Books, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5907; 200625; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 65)
      Crime and criminals; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5909; 200626; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 66)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Crime and criminals
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5911; 200627; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 67)
    - Security Mirror, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5913; 207095; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 68)
    - Shelving Books, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_re5915; 207096; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 69)
    - Entrance, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5917; 207097; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 70)
    - Merchandise Display, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5919; 207098; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 71)
    - Modeling Merchandise, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5921; 207099; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 72)
  - Breevort Hotel, circa 1890-1948; 207100 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th 9th Street, circa 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5924; 207101; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 3, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University. Real Estate.
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th Street, circa 1890; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5926; 207102; black-and-white print (photograph), 10 x 13 inches (Box 186, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Exteriors, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5927; 207103 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Corner of Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; 207104; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Awning, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5932; 207105; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Student in Front of Brittany Resident Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5934; 207172; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5936; 207173; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking North, 55 East 10th Street at Broadway, 1966; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5938; 207174; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 5)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University. Real Estate.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, 1965; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5940; 207175; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking West, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5942; 207176; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Folder 7)
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5944; 207177; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Broadway Windows, Undated; 207161 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5947; 207162; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Art.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5949; 207163; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Interiors, 1968-1984; 207164 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - View of Entrance Security Desk from Inside the Elevator, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; 207165; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Burglary Scene, Room 604, Brittany Residence Hall, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5954; 207166; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5956; 207167; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5958; 207168; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5960; 207169; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 5)
      Dwellings.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5962; 207170; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 6)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5964; 207171; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5966; 207178; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 8)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Dwellings.
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5968; 207188; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 9)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5969; 207189; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 10)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5972; 207190; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 11)